Guide to the Elsie H. Hillman Papers, 1920-2015 AIS.2013.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Other Political Activity, 1956-2012; III.
  - Personal Interactions with First Families, 1956-2012; 6.
    - George H.W. and Barbara Bush, 1978-2012
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, November 1, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, David Roderick to Elsie Hillman, December 3, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, A. J. F. O'Reilly to George H.W. Bush, February 18, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, March 16, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 22, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to John G. Brosky, May 15, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Arlin Adams to Elsie Hillman, September 14, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 12, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 7, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 1, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, Joseph W. Hagin to Elsie Hillman, February 9, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, February 14, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 17, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, Robert F. Koslow to George H.W. Bush, November 6, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Robert Barensfeld, November 27, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 4, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, Jennifer Fitzgerald to Elsie Hillman, February 12, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. April 1985 (Box 51, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, Jennifer Fitzgerald to Elsie Hillman, May 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, June 7, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 6, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 17, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 23, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 9, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 20, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 25, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 16, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, Albert Van Dusen to Elise Hillman, January 28, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 11, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 20, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 20, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 20, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 25, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 7, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 15, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 65)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 7, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 66)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 17, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 19, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 68)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, November 20, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 69)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 14, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 70)
      - Correspondence, Dorothy Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, Roy Hale to Elsie Hillman, c. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 72)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 21, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 73)
      - Correspondence, Jim Wray to Elsie Hillman, March 30, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 74)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 6, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 75)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 12, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 76)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush and Lee Atwater to Elsie Hillman, August 20, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 77)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, August 24, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 78)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, August 25, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 79)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 14, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 80)
      - Correspondence, Jennifer Fitzgerald to Elsie Hillman, October 2, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 81)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Henry Hillman, October 6, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 82)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 31, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 83)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 11, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 84)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 12, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 85)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Henry Hillman, November 12, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 86)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 7, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 87)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 11, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 88)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Henry Hillman, December 18, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 89)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1981-1987 (Box 51, Folder 90)
      - Correspondence, David Bates to Elsie Hillman, c.1987 (Box 51, Folder 91)
      - Correspondence, David Bates to Elsie Hillman, January 11, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 92)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 6, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 93)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 11, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 94)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 16, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 95)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 25, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 96)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 11, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 21, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 30, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Prescott S. Bush Jr. to Elsie Hillman, October 13, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 18, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 27, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Timothy Fisher to Elsie Hillman, November 15, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, November 17, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, John G. Brosky to Elsie Hillman, December 5, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, December 6, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to John G. Brosky, December 7, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Prescott S. Bush Jr. to Elsie Hillman, December 12, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 25, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Prescott S. Bush Jr. to Elsie Hillman, December 29, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, David Bates to Elsie Hillman, c.1988 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Note of Thanks After Electoral Victory, c.1988 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, c.1981-1989 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1981-1989 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 11, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 14, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 16, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 21, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 1, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 8, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, June 15, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 7, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Richard F. Morgan to Elsie Hillman, July 12, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 12, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 19, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Bettie (Unknown) to Elsie Hillman, October 2, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 21, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 30, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, December 12, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 12, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 15, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 14, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 2, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, April 4, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Joseph W. Haggin, April 19, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, Joseph Mahoney to Elsie Hillman, c. April 1990 (Box 52, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 30, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, October 5, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, George Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 14, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, Laura Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1990 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 12, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 23, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 11, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 26, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 17, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, Dan Quayle to Elsie Hillman, October 24, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 31, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, Jonathan Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 4, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, Cathy Fenton to Elsie Hillman, January 24, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, Don Rhodes to Elsie and Henry Hillman, January 31, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, April 10, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, Brent Scowcroft to Elsie Hillman, April 29, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, June 16, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 17, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence, Dan Quayle to Elsie Hillman, June 27, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 6, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, July 22, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 1, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 13, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 19, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence, George Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, November 12, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 65)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 9, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 66)
      - Correspondence, Charles Fagan to Elsie Hillman, December 14, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 68)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 13, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 69)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Henry Hillman, March 2, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 70)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, March 8, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, Prescott S. Bush Jr. to Elsie Hillman, April 12, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 72)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, May 18, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 73)
      - Correspondence, Rex Scouten to Elsie Hillman, July 21, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 74)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 5, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 75)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 22, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 76)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, January 1, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 77)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 4, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 78)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 6, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 79)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 7, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 80)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, April 17, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 81)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. and Barbara Bush, June 24, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 82)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. and Barbara Bush, July 5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 83)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 12, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 84)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 16, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 85)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 7, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 86)
      - Correspondence, Neil Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 11, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 87)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Neil Bush, January 17, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 88)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 21, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 89)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, August 16, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 90)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 1, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 91)
      - Correspondence, Clyde Slease to Elsie Hillman, December 20, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 92)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, January 11, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 22, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 8, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, June 25, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 16, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, March 13, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George W. Bush, April 4, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 11, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Jack Pidgeon, April 11, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 24, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 13, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Richard Kneedler, June 13, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 30, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, c. 1997 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, March 10, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 4, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 16, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Robert Mosbacher to Elsie Hillman, January 6, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 15, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Robert Mosbacher to Elsie Hillman, March 5, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Henry and Elsie Hillman, March 15, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 31, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 6, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, April 7, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 16, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 21, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Charles Hermann to Elsie Hillman, May 17, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 10, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 26, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, July 10, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, August 4, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 21, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 19, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 15, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 25, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 18, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, May 20, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George W. Bush, May 23, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 4, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 18, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 21, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 15, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, January 24, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 6, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, Mark Nordenberg to Elsie Hillman, February 20, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 5, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, August 30, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, September 6, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 14, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, September 20, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 27, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, Dayton Baker to Elsie Hillman, October 23, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, Brooke van Geertruyden to Dan Hudak, November 2, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, November 2, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 9, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, Jeb Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 11, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George W. and Laura, January 25, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Jeb and Columba Bush, January 25, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Marvin and Margaret Bush, January 25, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Neil and Sharon Bush, January 25, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Andrew Card, February 6, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Brad Blakeman, February 6, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Karen Hughes, February 6, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Karl Rove, February 6, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George W. Bush, February 8, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 65)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 12, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 66)
      - Correspondence, Richard S. Hamilton to Elsie Hillman, March 27, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 28, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 68)
      - Correspondence, Karl Rove to Elsie Hillman, April 1, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 69)
      - Correspondence, Nancy Holman to George W. Bush, April 4, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 70)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Marvin Bush, May 8, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George W. Bush, June 20, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 72)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. and Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 24, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 73)
      - Correspondence, George W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, September 13, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 74)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, October 4, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 75)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, October 7, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 76)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie and Henry Hillman, December 31, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 77)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Barbara Bush, March 1, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 78)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, March 10, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 79)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, April 29, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 80)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 9, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 81)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, June 29, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 82)
      - Correspondence, Colleen Ley to Elsie Hillman, December 16, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 83)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, December 16, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 84)
      - Correspondence, Tim Neff to George Bush, January 7, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 85)
      - Correspondence, Colleen Ley to Elsie Hillman, January 10, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 86)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, January 18, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 87)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to George H.W. Bush, January 26, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 88)
      - Correspondence, George H.W. Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 3, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 89)
      - Correspondence, Abraham Twerski to Laura Bush, February 7, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 90)
      - Correspondence, Maurice Cohill to Laura Bush, February 8, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 91)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Laura Bush, February 14, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 92)
      - Correspondence, Barbara Bush to Elsie Hillman, February 15, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 93)
      - Correspondence, Dorothy Bush Koch to Elsie Hillman, March 28, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 94)